David Adindu

CUSTOMER SERVICE PROFESSIONAL

Portfolio: https://DavidCJAdindu.github.io/Portfolio

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/david-adindu-0b71b71b6/

PROFILE

Personable, reliable customer service professional with 3 years of experience in a customer service environment. Exceptional staff member and team contributor with a positive attitude who consistently adds value and helps corporations reach their goals.

SKILLS

Attention to Detail | Politeness | Critical Thinking | Organisation | Self-discipline | Ability to Work Under Pressure | Customer Service | Communication | Cheerfulness | Active Listening | Empathy | Problem Solving | Time Management | Product Knowledge | Diligence | Negotiation | Sales | Positive Attitude | Passion for Technology | Programming | Blockchain

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Pennys Blanchardstown

Sales Assistant | 09/2018 - 01/2019

- Assisted customers per day by answering questions in a helpful and empathetic manner.
- Described consumer goods to customers, thoroughly explaining details and product usage.
- Assisted 50 new customers per day on average.
- Communicated details about promotions, customer programs and products, while providing exceptional customer service.
- Promoted customer loyalty by successfully handling customer's questions and complaints

Pizza Hut

Shift Manager | 05/2019 - 03/2020

- Assisted a driven and focused sales team to deliver exceptional customer service and achieve revenue targets.
- Developed positive relationships with customers to promote loyalty, increasing customer satisfaction.
- Promoted available products to customers to meet shoppers needs.
- Provided value to more than 80 people a day by consistently implementing my team management and customer service skills.

KFC Letterkenny

Team Member | 05/2021 - Present

- Assisting a driven and focused team to deliver exceptional customer service and achieve restaurant goals.
- Developing positive relationships with customers and team members to promote loyalty, increasing customer satisfaction and overall fulfilment within the organisation.
- Providing value to more than 50 people a day by consistently implementing my teamwork and customer service skills.

EDUCATION

Technological University Dublin (Blanchardstown) - Bachelor of Science (Computing)